ashop.com.au 2019-03-04

# Privacy Policy - Ecommerce Shopping Cart Software

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy ("Policy") describes how Ashop Commerce collects and uses the personal information you provide on the website http://www.Ashop.com.au ("Websites") which are owned and operated by Ashop Commerce (hereinafter "Ashop", "we", "us", "our"), and all associated Ashop services ("Services") provided by Ashop through these Websites.

###### Information Collection and Use

Ashop is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Ashop collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we determine we have collected personal information from a child younger than 13 years of age, we will take reasonable measures to remove that information from our systems.

###### Registration

In order to use this web site., a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.

###### Order

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

###### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to fully browse our online catalogue or order products online. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

###### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

###### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

###### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we [Ashop] are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

###### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

###### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as post code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

###### Security

This web site. takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site., your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link [www.thawte.com].

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

###### Special Offers

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

###### Site and Service Updates

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

###### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

###### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support.

###### Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking the “unsubscribe” link found within the promotional emails and changing your contact preferences. Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

###### EEA users

Individuals located in the European Economic Area (EEA) have certain rights in respect to their personal information, including the right to access, correct, or delete Personal Data we process through your use of our site. If you’re a user based in the EEA, you can:

  * Request a Personal Data report by contacting our support. This report will include the Personal Data we have about you, provided to you in a structured, commonly used, and portable format. Please note that we may request additional information from you to verify your identity before we disclose any information.
  * Have your Personal Data corrected or deleted. Some Personal Data can be updated by you: You can update your name and email address through your Ashop account settings.
  * Object to us processing your Personal Data. You can ask us to stop using your Personal Data, including when we use your Personal Data to send you marketing emails. We only send marketing communications to users located in the EEA with your prior consent, and you may withdraw your consent at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link found within the promotional emails and changing your contact preferences. Please note you will continue to receive transactional messages related to our Services, even if you unsubscribe from marketing emails.

###### Contact Us

Please refer any queries or complaints about our Privacy Policy or privacy issues to our:

PRIVACY OFFICER  
Ashop Commerce Pty Ltd  
ABN 80 111 256 896  
Level 3 17-19 Bridge St, Sydney NSW 2000 Australia  
Phone: +61 02 8103 4195  
Email: support@ashop.com.au

###### Effective Date of This Privacy

This Privacy Policy was first effective as of May 17, 2018.  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 17, 2018.
